[{"answer": "Of course I do..", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "My mother is", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I can think of a stronger word.  Are you okay", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " Where you from, my friend", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place?  Where's that", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't understand why you're so mad at me", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Get what", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hold on there", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I said you weren't on drugs, but I never said you were fine.  You're suffering from extreme fatigue and stress that manifested itself into one hell of an anxiety attack.  At least that's what we hope it is.  You had a major seizure, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't get it.  The couch is barely scorched.  And how can he burn from just the neck down", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It happens?  That's your explanation", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Call me crazy...but I think he's after that place.  The whole place.  In my dream he said something about needing a few souls to get the job done. I think he has to kill in order to get the power to suck in a new town", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Thank you.  There's more.  There are... other people in there.  In the nightmares", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm sorry.  It's all so hard to accept", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I've been in danger before. THAT I can handle", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I wish I could convince you of the danger you and the others are in", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "This is worse than anything you can imagine", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Wonderful", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm going to go to bed soon", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "But we have to catch him in the act to get him", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "They're not rules", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What's on your mind", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "A deal's what got me into this", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Leave my father out of this", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "After you make it look like this", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend!  You scared the shit out of me", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Where are the Dream Police", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Where are the Dream Police", "docId": "Nightmare-on-Elm-Street-The-Final-Chapter.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I do now.  Look what I found", "qsentId": 30}]